Finding Aid for the Collection of Material About the 1932 Los Angeles Olympic Games, 1932 LSC.2025
UCLA Library Special Collections
1932 Los Angeles Olympic Games collection of material
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.2025
2 oversize_boxes
2 boxes
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942327823606533
Scope and Content
Collection consists of programs, clippings, and souvenir materials relating to the 1932 Olympic Games in Los Angeles. Includes souvenir programs, stamps, cards, photographs, tickets, newspaper sections, scrapbooks, a map, pennants, flags, and rings. Also includes a complete run of official programs from July 30, 1932-August 14, 1932.
Additional Physical Form Available
A copy of the original version of this online finding aid is available at the UCLA Department of Special Collections for in-house consultation and may be obtained for a fee. Please contact:
Public Services Division
UCLA Library, Department of Special Collections
Room A1713, Charles E. Young Research Library
Box 951575
Los Angeles, CA 90095-1575
Telephone: 310/825-4988 (10:00 a.m. - 4:45 p.m., Pacific Time)
Email: spec-coll@library.ucla.edu
Olympic Games (10th: 1932: Los Angeles, Calif.)
- Olympics Games souvenir programs with sections about Los Angeles and California., 7 items. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Olympic Games souvenir programs., n.d.; 24 items. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Photographs., n.d.; 5 items. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Cultural and sports events relating to the Olympic Games--ephemera., 10 items. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Souvenir stamps., n.d.; 1 sheet. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Souvenir stamps., n.d.; 1 sheet. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Souvenir stamps., n.d.; 1 type, in 3 sections (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Olympic Games tickets; 1 envelope, 2 ticket application forms., n.d.; 33 items. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Olympic Games souvenir cards, bilder-gruppe 19, photochemical prints., n.d.; 51 items. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Olympic Games souvenir cards, bilder-gruppe 20, photochemical prints., n.d.; 51 items. (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Olympic Games souvenir cards, bilder-gruppe 21, photochemical prints., n.d.; 26 items. (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Olympic Games souvenir cards, bilder-gruppe 22, photochemical prints., n.d.; 26 items. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Olympic Games souvenir cards, bilder-gruppe 23, photochemical prints., n.d.; 51 items. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Souvenir viewbooks (photochemical prints connected by accordion folds, for mailing)., n.d.; 4 items. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Newspaper sections on the Olympic Games., n.d.; 7 items. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Olympic realia: pennants, flags, rings, etc.., n.d.; 40 items. (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Olympic history., n.d.; 3 items. (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Official programs, 10th Olympiad., July 30-31, 1932 and n.d.; 3 items. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Official programs, 10th Olympiad.., August 1-9, 1932 n.d.; 10 items. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Official programs, 10th Olympiad., August 10-14, 1932 and n.d.; 12 items. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Olympic Games stylized map, scroll, and empty cover from Olympic souvenir program., 3 items. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Scrapbook of the Olympic Games of 1932, in Los Angeles (1 of 2), Contains clippings, photographs, and related ephemera. Gift of Robert C. Carter, 1956. (Box 5)
- Scrapbook of the Olympic Games of 1932, in Los Angeles (2 of 2), Contains clippings, photographs, and related ephemera. Gift of Robert C. Carter, 1956. (Box 6)